Is Ernest Goes to Jail the only
prison movie you've seen?
(Sheldon:)It scared me straight, Leonard.
(knock on door)
(Barry:)Hey, I've been thinking.
(Barry:)I was being petty.
You can have my helium.
(Leonard:)Thank you, Barry.
(Barry:)But you have to add my name
to your paper.
(Sheldon:)That's preposterous.
(Barry:)I don't know, seems fair.
(Barry:)You can't do it without me.
(Leonard:)Can you give us a minute?
(Barry:)Take your time.
(Barry:)I'll walk out backwards
for dramatic effect.
(Man:)I don't like
being extorted like this.
(Sheldon:)Especially by him of all people.
(Leonard:)Me neither, but what
other choice do we have?
(Leonard:)I promise this is the last time.
(Leonard:)It says right here
on Wikipedia.
"A Mexican standoff is
a confrontation between
at least three parties."
(Sheldon:)How can you trust Wikipedia
if they use "between"
to refer to three parties?
(Helium Man:)They should've used
"among," right?
Or "amongst," if they were
feeling whimsically archaic.
(Sheldon:)All right,
enough with the chitchat.
(Helium Man:)Are we gonna watch
Ernest Goes to Jail or not?
(Sheldon:)Absolutely.
(Sheldon:)But don't be surprised
if this movie sets you
(Sheldon:)on the straight and narrow.
I am open to change.